

BENDEGÚZ ÁRON SINKOVICZ

IT FINANCE ANALYST

■ Bendeguzsinkovicz@gmail.com

+36 30 460 2533



Open to relocate



/bendeguz-aron-sinkovicz/



SUMMARY

Dedicated and self-motivated IT/Finance analyst with three years of professional experience at top rated multinational firms. Proven track record of providing financial and data analysis as well as automating tasks with a can do atitude. Ability to establish and maintain excellent relationship with international clients/colleagues. Looking forward to provide exceptional value while constantly challenging myself to stay ahead of competition.



EXPERIENCE

KPMG Global Services

Data Converter Specialist – Sep 2022

- Handle the full cycle of ETL process regarding VAT data using MSSQL/SQLite and KPMG owned programs.
- Writing/Testing C# embedded XML and Python code
- Providing data cleaning and transforming services for clients all over the world(EU, US, ASPAC, LATAM)
- Creating workflows in Alteryx, VBA.

BP – Financial Accountant May 2021 – Aug 2022

- Monthly closing activities, budgeting and forcasting
- Create financial reports with Excel and Power BI
- P&L and CashFlow analysis

CommerzBank - Accounting/regulatory reporting intern Apr 2020 – Apr 2021

- Created various financial reports using Cognos BI, SAP, SQL
- Responsible for creating and analyzing daily, monthly and quarterly reports for Hungarian National Bank
- Analyzing and calculating DCF loan model for more than hundred clients.

SKILLS

- ETL(SQL, Alteryx, VBA)
- Python(Pandas, Numpy, Scikit learn, Seaborn)
- **R**(dplyr, ggplot2)
- Statistical modeling(Hypothesis Testing, A/B testing)
- Machine Learning(Linear regression, classification, cluster analysis)
- Data visualization: Excel, Power BI, Matplotlib, Tableau

EDUCATION

Business Administration and Management (BSc) - University of **Pécs** Sept 2017 – June 2020

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: C1 level

SPANISH: A1 level

HUNGARIAN: Native

CERTIFICATES

Codecademy – Data Scientist, Data Analyst, R Programing, Tableau

Linkedin – Pricing Strategies, Power BI, Power Query, Power Pivot

Udemy – Financial Analyst 2021

AZ-900 Certificate